http://www.beattiegroup.com/legal-notice/

GIFTS TO REMEMBER AT CARTWRIGHT & BUTLER
TALKING RUBBISH WITH BIFFA - LEADING THE NATIONAL WASTE DEBATE
Glasgow
CALA (West)
Legal Notice
The following sets out the terms & conditions of use of the Beattie Communications Group website.
None of the services referred to on this website are available or appropriate for sale or use in any jurisdiction where such activity is prohibited. Any persons resident outside the United Kingdom who access this website must first satisfy themselves that they are not subject to any local requirements which prohibit or restrict them from doing so.
Our liability to you
The information contained in this website is not comprehensive. Despite our efforts, it may not be accurate, up to date or applicable to the circumstances of any particular case. We cannot accept any liability for any inaccuracies or omissions (other than for fraudulent misrepresentation) in this website and any decisions you make based on information contained in this website are your sole responsibility. Neither Beattie Communications Group nor any of its subsidiaries accept liability for any direct, indirect, special, consequential or other losses or damages of whatsoever kind arising out of access to, or the use of this website or any information contained in it. We are of course happy to discuss with you the implications of any issue raised if you e-mail us at info@beattiegroup.com.
No information contained in this website constitutes or would be deemed to constitute an invitation or inducement by or on behalf of Beattie Communications Group or any of its subsidiaries to enter into a contract with you. Other than in respect of personal information which will be treated in accordance with the Beattie Communications Group Privacy Statement, if you provide information to us, you agree that we have unlimited rights to such information and that we may use such information in any way we choose. Such information shall be deemed to be non-confidential.
Beattie Communications Group accepts no liability for any direct, indirect, special, consequential or other losses or damages of whatsoever kind arising out of access to, or use of, any hyperlinked website, or any information contained therein.
Forward Looking Statements
Statements made on or contained in this website or in documents referred to are or may be forward looking statements. Such statements reflect the views of Beattie Communications Group as of the date made with respect to future events and are subject to risks and uncertainties. Actual results may differ from those expressed in such statements, depending on a variety of factors including future levels of industry product supply; demand and pricing; political stability and economic growth; development and use of new technology; actions of competitors; and natural disasters, wars and acts of terrorism.
Ownership of the copyright of this website
The copyright in the contents and any downloads from this website is owned by Beattie Communications Group Ltd or its subsidiaries unless otherwise stated. All rights are reserved by Beattie Communications Group Ltd, 118 North Main Street, Carronshore, Falkirk, FK2 8HU.
You are responsible for obeying all applicable copyright laws. We permit you to make copies of this website as necessary incidental acts during your viewing of it; and you may take a print for your personal use of so much of the website as is reasonable for private purposes. All other use is strictly prohibited.
Use of any Hyperlink
Neither Beattie Communications Group nor any of its subsidiaries are responsible for the content of any other website, including any website through which you may have gained access to our website or to which you may gain access from our website. We do not accept any liability in connection with any such websites or links.
Where Beattie Communications Group provide a hyperlink to a third party's website, we do so in good faith, believing that such a website contains or may contain material which is relevant to that on our website. Such a hyperlink does not signify that Beattie Communications Group or its subsidiaries have reviewed or approve of the connected third party's website or its contents - indeed in certain instances a hyperlink may connect you to a third party's website containing views contradictory to those expressed on our website or otherwise held by Beattie Communications Group and its subsidiaries.
What law governs this website?
Your use of this website and downloads from it, and the operation of these terms and conditions, shall be governed in accordance with the laws of Scotland. The Scottish courts shall have exclusive jurisdiction over any dispute arising out of your use of this website.
In the event that any or any part of the terms contained in these terms and conditions shall be determined by any competent authority to be invalid, unlawful or unenforceable to any extent, such term shall to that extent be severed from the remaining terms which shall continue to be valid and enforceable to the fullest extent permitted by law.
Privacy Statement
The following sets out the privacy policy of use of the Beattie Communications Group website.
Beattie Communications Group respects your privacy and is committed to protecting it. We provide this Privacy Statement to inform you of our Privacy Policy and practices and of the choices you can make about the way your information is collected online and how that information is used.
Data automatically collected
We, like many companies, automatically collect the following information:
Technical information, including the type of device you’re using, the IP address, browser and operating system being used to connect your computer to the internet.
Information about how you use the website e.g. we collect information about the pages you visit and how you navigate the website
This information is used to improve the services that we offer. We do not link information automatically logged by such means with personal data about specific individuals.
Cookies
To stop cookies being placed on your computer please refer to your specific Internet browser for instructions. The cookies we place on your computer are known as 'ASP.NET_SessionId' and expire at the end of your session. In a few cases blocking cookies may reduce the functionality of some websites or prevent access to them depending on your chosen browser options.
Cookies are small pieces of information that are stored on your computer by the server maintaining and operating the website. They do not compromise your privacy or security as they store a randomly generated identifying tag on your computer.
Data collection and use
When you request information through this website, we may need to know some personal information about you. When emailing us, or subscribing for free news or information we need your e-mail address, name and other limited personal identifiers, typically name and contact number.
Where you request employment related services or products we will usually need limited data about personal identifiers, education, employment, family and financial details.
Your personal data will be processed to provide information, goods, products and services you request in the form that you require.
If we require sensitive personal data then we will ensure that the collection and use is in strict accordance with the "applicable legislation" principles of data protection and data privacy.
Since Beattie Communications Group operates globally, the information you submit may be transferred outside of the European Economic Area (“EEA”). This and all other transmissions will remain secure and under our sole control and will not be transferred to any third parties. If we transfer your information outside of the EEA we will take steps to ensure appropriate security measures are taken with the aim of ensuring that your privacy rights continue to be protected as outlined in this policy.
If we look to use your personal data for a new purpose, beyond what it was originally provided for, we will ask for your consent.
Legal Basis for Using You Data
We are required to set out the legal basis for our processing of your personal data.
We consider the following grounds to be relevant:
As necessary for the pursuit of our legitimate interests including:-
Promoting, marketing and advertising our services
Understand how people interact with our website
Preventing, investigating and detecting crime or fraud
Enhance, personalise or otherwise improve our services / communications for the benefit of our customers
Legal Obligation For compliance with legal and regulatory requirements
Specific Consent Where you have provided specific consent to us on using your personal information e.g. to send you email marketing
Data retention
We will not retain your data for longer than necessary for the purpose for which it is collected.
Your rights
Under UK data protection law, you have certain rights over the personal information that we hold about. These rights include:
To be informed about how we use your personal data (the purpose of this Privacy Statement)
To have inaccurate personal information corrected. If you believe that the information we hold is inaccurate or out of date please contact us by emailing info@beattiegroup.com or post (see details below)
You may ask us to delete your personal data. We will do so if there are no legal exceptions that require us to retain it. We may, in certain circumstances, anonymise rather than delete it.
You have a right to request access (unless legal exception apply) to the personal data that we hold about you. To request access to your information please send a description of the information you want to see and proof of your identity to Human Resources, Beattie Communications Group, 118 North Main Street, Carronshore, Falkirk, FK2 8HU
You have the right to ask us to restrict the processing of your personal data if there is a disagreement about its accuracy or we’re not lawfully allowed to use it
You have the right to review automated decision-making or profiling.
Disclosure and Visitor choice
You may unsubscribe or opt-out of services at any time. Details of how to opt-out of the Beattie Communications Group website are available and is a simple process. Where we disclose your personal data for those purposes stated, we provide you with the means to opt-out of disclosure by either indicating in a box at the point of the website where personal data is collected, by sending an email to info@beattiegroup.com or by posting a request to Human Resources, Beattie Communications Group, 118 North Main Street, Carronshore, Falkirk, FK2 8HU. Where we disclose your personal data for purposes, which are different to those, stated we offer you the opportunity to consent prior to disclosure.
Children
Beattie Communications Group is committed to protecting the privacy needs of children and we encourage parents and guardians to take an active role in their children's online activities and interests. Beattie Communications Group does not knowingly collect information from children under the age of 13 and Beattie Communications Group does not target its websites to children under 13.
Security
Beattie Communications Group have implemented security policies, rules and technical measures to protect the personal data that we have under our control that complies with data privacy & protection legislation appropriate to the jurisdiction applicable to the website. The security measures are designed to prevent unauthorised access, improper use or disclosure, unauthorised modification & unlawful destruction or accidental loss.
Privacy compliance
We are committed to complying with UK data privacy legislation. Data privacy legislation is subject to revision and we strongly suggest that you regularly check our privacy statement.
Hyperlinks
The Beattie Communications Group website may provide links to third-party websites for your convenience and information. If you access those links, you will leave the Beattie Communications Group website. Beattie Communications Group does not control those websites or their privacy practices, which may differ from that of Beattie Communications Group. We do not endorse or make any representations about third-party websites. The Beattie Communications Group's Privacy Statement does not cover the personal data you choose to give to unrelated third parties. We encourage you to review the privacy policy of any company before submitting your personal information. Some third-party companies may choose to share their personal data with Beattie Communications Group; that sharing is governed by that third-party company's privacy policy.
Company Information
Beattie Communications Group Limited, Registered Office: 118 North Main Street, Carronshore, Falkirk, FK2 8HU. Incorporate in Scotland with company number SC248915. VAT number 817 1974 11.
© Copyright Beattie Communications Group Ltd 2018
All Services
PR
Digital
Social
Content Marketing
Film
Amazon
TALKING RUBBISH WITH BIFFA - LEADING THE NATIONAL WASTE DEBATE
CALA (West)
